<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Nick Frosst&#39;s personal site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Nick Frosst&#39;s personal site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:52:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>music</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/music/</guid>
      <description>I play in an indie pop rock band called Good Kid. We play fast paced good time music :) We currently have a combined 5 million+ plays on spotify, and have played shows in New York, La, and around Ontario. We are currently working on our second EP. It should be done soon I swear.
some links: website spotify youtube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>other art</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/other_art/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/other_art/</guid>
      <description>I run a bi-monthly sea shanty night at the imperial pub. We drink beer and sing old songs. All are welcome. If you are interested please join our mailing list .
I am interested in 3d photography, and work with the nishika n8000 camera to create wiggle grams which I post on instagram.
I am an avid gunpla builder. These I post nowhere. I am not good at it, and dont plan on improving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speaking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/speaking/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy teaching and am actively trying to improve at it. So I normally say yes when someone asks me to speak. I have given guest lectures at U of T, Ryerson, and York University at the graduate and undergradute level. I have spoken at the Toronto Machine Learning Summit, Re.Work AI conference, Start AI, Scotia Bank learning days, and others.
Here is a video of a talk I gave recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>writing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/writing/</guid>
      <description>Selected Academic work:
Sabour, Sara, Nicholas Frosst, and Geoffrey E. Hinton. &amp;ldquo;Dynamic routing between capsules.&amp;rdquo; Advances in neural information processing systems. 2017.
Sabour, Sara, Nicholas Frosst, and Geoffrey Hinton. &amp;ldquo;Matrix capsules with EM routing.&amp;rdquo; 6th international conference on learning representations, ICLR. 2018.
Frosst, Nicholas, and Geoffrey Hinton. &amp;ldquo;Distilling a neural network into a soft decision tree.&amp;rdquo; arXiv preprint arXiv:1711.09784 (2017).
Frosst, Nicholas, Sara Sabour, and Geoffrey Hinton. &amp;ldquo;DARCCC: Detecting adversaries by reconstruction from class conditional capsules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/menu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/resume/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>